<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>krag.org Archives &bull; krag.be</title>
	<atom:link href="/index.php/category/kragorg/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>I am multiple and various - Tomas A. Krag</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2004 08:50:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://i0.wp.com/krag.be/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/cropped-avatar_yuge-1.jpg?fit=32%2C32&#038;ssl=1</url>
	<title>krag.org Archives &bull; krag.be</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">124264715</site>	<item>
		<title>I never wanted to be my own boss</title>
		<link>/index.php/2004/10/20/i-never-wanted-to-be-my-own-boss/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/2004/10/20/i-never-wanted-to-be-my-own-boss/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2004 08:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[krag.org]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mixed Bag]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=466</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Well mine wasn&#8217;t. I don&#8217;t think i&#8217;ve ever wanted that, in fact i&#8217;ve often shied away from it, during the dot-com heydey, and consciously chosen the boring default. I&#8217;m not sure why exactly, whether it&#8217;s sharing a name with the unbelieving apostle, cowardice, conveniene or just high resilience to bs. It doesn&#8217;t really matter after [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2004/10/20/i-never-wanted-to-be-my-own-boss/">I never wanted to be my own boss</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Well mine wasn&#8217;t. I don&#8217;t think i&#8217;ve ever wanted that, in fact i&#8217;ve often shied away from it, during the dot-com  heydey, and consciously chosen the boring default. I&#8217;m not sure why exactly, whether it&#8217;s sharing a name with the unbelieving apostle, cowardice, conveniene or just high resilience to bs.<br />
It doesn&#8217;t really matter after all, the point I wanted to make was that I never dreamed of being my own boss, i would have been contented working for other people all my life. in fact I think I would mostly prefer to be part of a team, with limited responsibility for having to make it all make sense (and money). </p>
<p>Yet here I am, running a small non-profit with Sebastian. Responsible for my own destiny, our success, and a lot of other high-brow things.  It just happened this way. I found the ideal business in ict&#8217;s for the developing world, in which i had more fun, more fullfillment, and more interesting challenges in 3 month than i would have in a year of web agency, dot-not mayhem. I knew that that was what i wanted to work with, and i took the only path that presented itself to me. being my own boss.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s haunting me now. I can&#8217;t help but feel misplaced in so many ways. I can&#8217;t help but dream of having a regular job, with colleagues, limited responsibility, and the ability to run away screaming if it all becomes too much. Perhaps that&#8217;s really what it is, a fear of being trapped. trapped in a construct i invented, trapped in a job that i don&#8217;t really want, but can&#8217;t run away from, because that would be running away from myself and my dream. </p>
<p>i think that&#8217;s probably a large part of it. it&#8217;s a responsibility i never wanted, but having taken it upon myself, despite this fat, i need to deal with it or find a way out that leaves at least a few bridges standing. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2004/10/20/i-never-wanted-to-be-my-own-boss/">I never wanted to be my own boss</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/2004/10/20/i-never-wanted-to-be-my-own-boss/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">466</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>I’m launching a new blog</title>
		<link>/index.php/2002/06/06/im-launching-a-new-blog/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2002 12:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[krag.org]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m launching a new blog called m u l t i p l i c i t y It can be found at multiplicity.dk I want to invite other interesting people to participate in my blog, and for that purpose krag.org was the wrong name&#8230;.. I&#8217;ll leaeve this up for a while, since there are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/06/06/im-launching-a-new-blog/">I’m launching a new blog</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m launching a new blog called m u l t i p l i c i t y</p>
<p>It can be found at <a href="http://www.multiplicity.dk/">multiplicity.dk</a></p>
<p>I want to invite other interesting people to participate in my blog, and for that purpose krag.org was the wrong name&#8230;..</p>
<p>I&#8217;ll leaeve this up for a while, since there are a lot of links to this site, and since I want people to be able to get at the archives from here, but since I want a clean slate, I won&#8217;t be moving the entries from this blog to my new one.</p>
<p>Enjoy the multiplicity of life&#8230;.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/06/06/im-launching-a-new-blog/">I’m launching a new blog</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">169</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>It’s my 28th birthday soon.</title>
		<link>/index.php/2002/01/29/its-my-28th-birthday-soon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2002 09:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[krag.org]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=116</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s my 28th birthday soon. Which, all things considering is probably not such a bad thing. Considering it&#8217;s damn close to a year since my last one. People tell me that&#8217;s not only quite normal, but one of the easiest ways to get older. As usual theres a wish list here, for those that care, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/01/29/its-my-28th-birthday-soon/">It’s my 28th birthday soon.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s my 28th birthday soon. Which, all things considering is probably not such a bad thing. Considering it&#8217;s damn close to a year since my last one. People tell me that&#8217;s not only quite normal, but one of the easiest ways to get older. As usual theres a wish list <a href="http://www.krag.org/Blog/wishlist.shtml">here</a>, for those that care, or those that are just plain curious what I have come up with this time. </p>
<p>Apart from the fact that I&#8217;m getting older (as usual) and my hair-line is receding (as usual) and there&#8217;s a good bit of aggresive energy at work (more than usual), caused by deadlines looming like mountains on the horizon, I&#8217;m really quite well.<br />
A number of my more esoteric, altruistic projects are moving along, while others seem to have ground to a complete halt. I have (not for the first time) completely given up any ideas of becoming a sophist or even a nihilist to ease my mind of growing worries that the world I happen to inhabit is indeed a fucked up place full of egotistical maniacs with entirely too much power.</p>
<p>The new Danish governments pretty obvious attempt at &#8216;cleaning&#8217; Denmark of too many foreign influences.<br />
The infamous G.W. Bush&#8217;es strange meanderings into Cuban politics to avoid extending any human (or civil) rights to the admittedly not-so-nice &#8216;enemy&#8217;.<br />
The misery of world poverty, lack of tolerance and general stupidity.<br />
All these, and many more things, leave me numbed and slightly depresed, now that flirts with various forms of not caring have been tossed down the drain. The fact is, I do care, and that ca be pretty tough.</p>
<p>I have to say that  last nights trip to the Computer Game Cafe, down the street, with a handful of friends for a serious battle of Counter-Strike helped release some of the agression. For a time <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/01/29/its-my-28th-birthday-soon/">It’s my 28th birthday soon.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">116</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>My good friend Lura just</title>
		<link>/index.php/2002/01/22/my-good-friend-lura-just/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2002 10:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[krag.org]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=110</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>My good friend Lura just e-mailed me this link, which she in turn received from a friend in Ghana. Apparently Ghanaian website GhanaWeb.com has used an old picture to illustrate the broad support for the Ghanaian Black-Stars football team during the current African NAtions Cup in Mali. Now click the link, and play a game [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/01/22/my-good-friend-lura-just/">My good friend Lura just</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>My good friend Lura just e-mailed me this <a href="http://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/NewsArchive/photo.day.php?ID=21013">link</a>, which she in turn received from a friend in Ghana. Apparently Ghanaian website GhanaWeb.com has used an old picture to illustrate the broad support for the Ghanaian Black-Stars football team during the current African NAtions Cup in Mali. Now click the link, and play a game of &#8220;spot the overweight, white-assed Black-Star supporter. Oh, and the lovely girl in the picture is of course Lura.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/01/22/my-good-friend-lura-just/">My good friend Lura just</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">110</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Next to my job here</title>
		<link>/index.php/2002/01/18/next-to-my-job-here/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2002 13:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[krag.org]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=106</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Next to my job here at Pink Floor, I&#8217;ve been working on a few projects of my own. My interests lie somewhere in thr vacuum between wireless technologies, open-source systems, and IT in the developing world. I really want to, no need to work with developing world problems, but there is the basic necessity of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/01/18/next-to-my-job-here/">Next to my job here</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Next to my job here at <a href="http://www.pinkfloor.dk/" title="Pink FLoor">Pink Floor</a>, I&#8217;ve been working on a few projects of my own. My interests lie somewhere in thr vacuum between wireless technologies, open-source systems,  and IT in the developing world. </p>
<p>I really want to, no need to work with developing world problems, but there is the basic necessity of making money, and the desire to geek out from time to time. Get involved with technology, the immediate satisfaction of getting something to work, versus the long-term startegic philosophising of so many other projects. </p>
<p>So to boost my chances of making a living as a consultant in the Danish Internet world, while pursuing developing world projects, i&#8217;ve decided to attempt writing a weblog specifically on wireless technologies, and specifically from a danish perspective. There really isn&#8217;t an idependent view of what&#8217;s happening with mobile Internet, wireless ethernet, and related technologies and applications in Denmark.<br />
The biggest issue is whether or not I can find the time to update it regularly, and of course whether I can find an interested group of readers here.<br />
The blog is in english, to make it easier for the world at large, that is if they have any interest in this sort of thing. You can find the first installments on the <a href="http://www.mostlyharmless.dk/">Mostly Harmless</a> webpage or directly at <a href="http://wireless.mostlyharmless.dk/">http://wireless.mostlyharmless.dk/</a>. </p>
<p>In terms of projects, I am still working with my good friend and former colleague Sebastian on an action plan for developing technologies specifically for developing world markets, starting of with a solar or wind powered 802.11b base station and linux community server. And I&#8217;m also working with another good friend and former colleague, Charlotte, on starting a think Tank for IT people with a Social Conscience. Well, that&#8217;s the working title, and exactly waht it will contain is as yet completely unknown, but at the very least a forum for discussing and getting feedback on these absurd projects I keep getting involved in.</p>
<p>And Remember: &#8220;In this day and age, the only thing that gives you more freedom than loads of money is the realization that you don&#8217;t need money!&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/01/18/next-to-my-job-here/">Next to my job here</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">106</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The wonderful people at GeekCorps</title>
		<link>/index.php/2002/01/11/the-wonderful-people-at-geekcorps/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2002 15:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[krag.org]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=104</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The wonderful people at GeekCorps offered me a return to Ghana with the new team. A perfect project, working with mobile Internet and WAP for a company called Rancard Solutions in Accra. Leave in late february for 4 months. Combine mobile internet and the digital divide, the 2 areas that hold my interest, as well [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/01/11/the-wonderful-people-at-geekcorps/">The wonderful people at GeekCorps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The wonderful people at <a href="http://www.geekcorps.org/" title="GeekCorps">GeekCorps</a> offered me a return to Ghana with the new team. A perfect project, working with mobile Internet and WAP for a company called <a href="http://www.rancardsolutions.com/">Rancard Solutions</a> in Accra. Leave in late february for 4 months. Combine mobile internet and the digital divide, the 2 areas that hold my interest, as well as two areas i see as highly complementary.</p>
<p>Unfortunately I am in the middle of a contract that i can&#8217;t really leave until early April at the earliest, and who knows what I want to be doing then. So at the moment I am asking other people I know who have expertise in WAP and Java, wether they&#8217;d be interested in having that great experience. If you know anyone, dash me an e-mail address.</p>
<p>So at the moment, I am looking into popping over to Ghana for a shorter period when this current project allows me the time. A sort of combined vacation and checking out the old haunts, maybe even lend a hand to some IT firms. We&#8217;ll see if I can actually afford it, and find the time in overlapping periods. </p>
<p>But at least it&#8217;s nice to start the week-end of dreaming a little bit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/01/11/the-wonderful-people-at-geekcorps/">The wonderful people at GeekCorps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">104</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>While teaching myself a little</title>
		<link>/index.php/2002/01/09/while-teaching-myself-a-little/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2002 16:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[krag.org]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=103</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While teaching myself a little bit about the problems of designing arabic websites, I came a cross a feature of HTML 4.0, which enables you to mirror pages for viewing Right-to-Left instead of Left-to-Right. Admittedly it only seems to work in Internet Explorer, and it&#8217;s meant for languages that are written that way round. However [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/01/09/while-teaching-myself-a-little/">While teaching myself a little</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While teaching myself a little bit about the problems of designing arabic websites, I came a cross a feature of HTML 4.0, which enables you to mirror pages for viewing Right-to-Left instead of Left-to-Right. Admittedly it only seems to work in Internet Explorer, and it&#8217;s meant for languages that are written that way round. However as a small test, I have made a version of my homepage that is mirrored. Click <a href="index.shtml?rtl">here </a>to try it out, and <a href="index.shtml">here</a> to get back to normal.<br />
&#8211;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/01/09/while-teaching-myself-a-little/">While teaching myself a little</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">103</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>On a tuesday night in</title>
		<link>/index.php/2002/01/08/on-a-tuesday-night-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2002 16:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[krag.org]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=102</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On a tuesday night in the new year. it&#8217;s 2002. another new beginning, a time to realize those dreams, or at least dream new ones. i&#8217;m here in copenhagen, still dreaming about working with it applications in the developing world while i slave away in the slightly more mainstream part of the business. still the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/01/08/on-a-tuesday-night-in/">On a tuesday night in</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On a tuesday night in the new year. it&#8217;s 2002. another new beginning, a time to realize those dreams, or at least dream new ones.<br />
i&#8217;m here in copenhagen, still dreaming about working with it applications in the developing world while i slave away in the slightly more mainstream part of the business. </p>
<p>still the same problem, i have all the ambitions to do something radically different, but don&#8217;t really have the guts to go with them. the will to throw myself at the problem with so much fearlessness and panache, that i can only succeed or fail miserably. i need to borrow some fearless meandering fom someone out there.</p>
<p>on the other hand, in the past year and a half, i have managed to quit a perfectly good and well-paying job, to ship myself to ghana as a volunteer. returning to denmark in april last year i had the guts to try and start my own company in a receding market, just because i couldn&#8217;t seem to find a job that suited my ambitions, and the dream still hasn&#8217;t died. </p>
<p>i recently thought, maybe i should start doing some spoken word stuff, you know poetry to music,<br />
try to write some rhymes,<br />
deal them out sour as limes,<br />
in these creative times,<br />
somewhere else to parcel desires<br />
apart from dreams less wires,<br />
in some developing world.</p>
<p>i miss writing more regularly, to have a purpose with writing, to try and express something. maybe i&#8217;ll be miserable at that more structured style, but maybe it would be fun. i don&#8217;t know, can&#8217;t tell, never will.<br />
but maybe i&#8217;ll give it a try.</p>
<p>oh, and i&#8217;ve decided to see if i cn find somewhere to continue my interrupted studies. highest on my wishlist is the MIT Digital Nations programme, but maybe less can do the job. another idea that i have no idea wether will happen or not, but it gives me something to aim for. </p>
<p>well, so long for now. cheers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2002/01/08/on-a-tuesday-night-in/">On a tuesday night in</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">102</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happy Holidays and a great</title>
		<link>/index.php/2001/12/20/happy-holidays-and-a-great/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2001 10:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[krag.org]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=101</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Happy Holidays and a great f&#8230;. blast of a New Year to everyone out there I know!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2001/12/20/happy-holidays-and-a-great/">Happy Holidays and a great</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Happy Holidays and a great f&#8230;. blast of a New Year to everyone out there I know!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2001/12/20/happy-holidays-and-a-great/">Happy Holidays and a great</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">101</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>I just posted a X-mas</title>
		<link>/index.php/2001/12/05/i-just-posted-a-x-mas/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2001 13:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[krag.org]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I just posted a X-mas 2001 wishlist in danish. You can find it here.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2001/12/05/i-just-posted-a-x-mas/">I just posted a X-mas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I just posted a X-mas 2001 wishlist in danish. You can find it <a href="wishlist.shtml">here</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2001/12/05/i-just-posted-a-x-mas/">I just posted a X-mas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">100</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
