<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Gadgets Archives &bull; krag.be</title>
	<atom:link href="/index.php/category/gadgets/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>I am multiple and various - Tomas A. Krag</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2003 09:23:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://i0.wp.com/krag.be/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/cropped-avatar_yuge-1.jpg?fit=32%2C32&#038;ssl=1</url>
	<title>Gadgets Archives &bull; krag.be</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">124264715</site>	<item>
		<title>This is the laptop I dream of</title>
		<link>/index.php/2003/09/30/this-is-the-laptop-i-dream-of/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/2003/09/30/this-is-the-laptop-i-dream-of/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2003 09:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gadgets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=408</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EmperorLinux &#8220;Meteor&#8221; Linux Laptop This past month I have travelled a lot. I&#8217;ve been on the road for about 22 days of the month, and for the first time I&#8217;ve really felt the downsides of my massive Dell Inspiron 8100, which weighs in at over 3.5 kg with the dual batteries and everything. Yes it&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2003/09/30/this-is-the-laptop-i-dream-of/">This is the laptop I dream of</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a title="EmperorLinux "Meteor" Linux Laptop" href="http://emperorlinux.com/meteor.html">EmperorLinux &#8220;Meteor&#8221; Linux Laptop</a></p>
<p>This past month I have travelled a lot. I&#8217;ve been on the road for about 22 days of the month, and for the first time I&#8217;ve really felt the downsides of my massive Dell Inspiron 8100, which weighs in at over 3.5 kg with the dual batteries and everything. Yes it&#8217;s a great machine with an incredible display, but to be honest I mostly use it in 2 places, at home and at the office. </p>
<p>I originally got it, because having a single machine to work with everywhere made a lot of sense, but more and more of my work is done on-line anyway, and my syncing skills are improving quickly. and the more I travel, the more I fancy an ultra-lite laptop, perhaps combined with an external monitor and keyboard at the office. </p>
<p>There is absolutely no way I can afford a new laptop at the moment, and that will probably be true for the foreseeable future, but that doesn&#8217;t prevent me from dreaming, and this linux-baby (Sharp MM10 revamped) from <a href="http://emperorlinux.com/">Emperor Linux</a> is absolutely gorgeous. And the fact that it can be an external harddrive through a USB 2.0 dock, is really enticing. And I&#8217;ve long wanted a crusoe processor, for their low-power tech, and because I like the idea of supporting someone other than Intel and AMD for a change. </p>
<p>Perhaps I can save some by buying the Sharp notebook, and installing linux myself. On the other hand, having emperor&#8217;s word for the fact that the main features are supported is quite a nice thing too. Oh well, keep dreaming <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p><bq>EmperorLinux supplies the Sharp Actius MM10 laptop pre-installed with Linux.<br />
We call the Sharp MM10 running Linux the &#8220;Meteor&#8221;. It is the thinnest and lightest Linux laptop we have ever offered. The Meteor is about the size of a very thin textbook (one-half-inch thick), and yet 2-pound feather-weight is a &#8220;real&#8221; computer. With the innovative USB cradle, you can even mount the system drive from another PC to sync your data! The Meteor MM10 features full Linux hardware support for: X, sound, USB, PCMCIA, WiFi, networking, and more.</bq></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2003/09/30/this-is-the-laptop-i-dream-of/">This is the laptop I dream of</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/2003/09/30/this-is-the-laptop-i-dream-of/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">408</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SMTP blues</title>
		<link>/index.php/2003/07/30/smtp-blues/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/2003/07/30/smtp-blues/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2003 09:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gadgets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=387</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I propose a web-based service that takes a shot at guessing an smtp-server that is open for the particular network you are connecting from. It would do a reverse lookup on the IP, , find the domain of the ISP you&#8217;re connecting from, and then try to ping mail.domain.com and smtp.domain.com and show me the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2003/07/30/smtp-blues/">SMTP blues</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I propose a web-based service that takes a shot at guessing an smtp-server that is open for the particular network you are connecting from.</p>
<p>It would do a reverse lookup on the IP, , find the domain of the ISP you&#8217;re connecting from, and then try to ping mail.domain.com and smtp.domain.com and show me the best-bet smtp servers.</p>
<p>Perhaps a small java-based client app that did the same, and then<br />
automatically tests whether the smtp server is open to relaying from your current machine would be even better. An app that runs on the Java MIDP profile so prevalent on smartphones and pda&#8217;s.</p>
<p>WHY?<br />
<span id="more-387"></span><br />
Well, as some of you know already, I have a WiFi enabled Handheld computer. The one and only, wonderful <a href="http://www.infosyncworld.com/hardware/handhelds/n/206.html">Palm Tungsten C</a>. And owning this handheld, wireless enabled device has shown me the usefullness of free, open wireless networks. Instead of having to bring out my 3 kg dell laptop, wait 3 minutes for it to boot, and then try to connect to a network that doesn&#8217;t exist, I can whip out my palm, and be on-line in a matter of seconds, rather than dozens of minutes. </p>
<p>I do it a lot. I check my mail, I update the weather forecast, and read up on my favourite blogs via blogstreets excellent <a href="http://rss.blogstreet.com/">rss2imap aggregation</a>. </p>
<p>I have seen a small wink of a ubiwuitous future, and I like it. The only problem is that I can&#8217;t really send e-mail without knowing an smtp server that&#8217;s open for me. The palm seems to have some issues with POP authentication for SMTP, my server doesn&#8217;t run ESMTP, and I have little desire to set-up and monitor an open relay, even if it is on a non-standard port and completely obscure ip. </p>
<p>I could use the palm&#8217;s built-in PPTP VPN client, but some firewalls won&#8217;t pass-through PPTP, and  besides, I want a generic solution to the problem, that I can use with my laptop, smartphone or any other device.</p>
<p>What say you?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2003/07/30/smtp-blues/">SMTP blues</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/2003/07/30/smtp-blues/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">387</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>2 new WiFi Digital camera’s</title>
		<link>/index.php/2003/07/23/2-new-wifi-digital-cameras/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2003 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gadgets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=383</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Almost simultaneous announcements of WiFi enebaled Digital Camera&#8217;s from Nikon and Fuji. Fuji&#8217;s is a 3 megapixel prototype, while Nikon&#8217;s is a high-end sports-camera with a WiFi add-on. Both announcements via Gizmodo, the ultimate gadget-site. Gizmodo : Fuji&#8217;s WiFi digital camera Gizmodo : It&#8217;s official: Nikon&#8217;s new D2H digital SLR camera Official announcement of Nikon&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2003/07/23/2-new-wifi-digital-cameras/">2 new WiFi Digital camera’s</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Almost simultaneous announcements of WiFi enebaled Digital Camera&#8217;s from Nikon and Fuji.</p>
<p>Fuji&#8217;s is a 3 megapixel prototype, while Nikon&#8217;s is a high-end sports-camera with a WiFi add-on.</p>
<p>Both announcements via Gizmodo, the ultimate gadget-site.</p>
<p><a title="Gizmodo : Fuji's WiFi digital camera" href="http://www.gizmodo.com/archives/007644.php">Gizmodo : Fuji&#8217;s WiFi digital camera</a></p>
<p><a title="Gizmodo : It's official: Nikon's new D2H digital SLR camera" href="http://www.gizmodo.com/archives/007771.php">Gizmodo : It&#8217;s official: Nikon&#8217;s new D2H digital SLR camera</a></p>
<p><bq>Official announcement of Nikon&#8217;s new digital SLR aimed at sports and news photographers, the four-megapixel D2H. The high-speed D2H has a new type of imaging sensor called a Junction Field Effect Transistor for shooting up to eight frames per second, and (here&#8217;s what so hot about this camera) an optional WiFi transmitter which can automatically upload images to a host PC over a wireless LAN.</bq></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2003/07/23/2-new-wifi-digital-cameras/">2 new WiFi Digital camera’s</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">383</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
