<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Me Archives &bull; krag.be</title>
	<atom:link href="/index.php/category/me/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>I am multiple and various - Tomas A. Krag</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 09:47:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://i0.wp.com/krag.be/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/cropped-avatar_yuge-1.jpg?fit=32%2C32&#038;ssl=1</url>
	<title>Me Archives &bull; krag.be</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">124264715</site>	<item>
		<title>Non-profit software developers summit</title>
		<link>/index.php/2011/11/20/non-profit-software-developers-summit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 09:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Me]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[non-profit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=804</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I took a break from my paternity leave to come to San Francisco and meet with about 100 other folks who work in the intersection of tech and social change. It&#8217;s a yearly event held by Aspiration, and facilitated by my close friend and mentor Gunner. It&#8217;s 3 days of insane mind-meld with some of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2011/11/20/non-profit-software-developers-summit/">Non-profit software developers summit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I took a break from my paternity leave to come to San Francisco and meet with about 100 other folks who work in the intersection of tech and social change. It&#8217;s a yearly event held by <a href="http://aspirationtech.org/events/devsummit11">Aspiration</a>, and facilitated by my close friend and mentor Gunner. </p>
<p>It&#8217;s 3 days of insane mind-meld with some of the smartest and most passionate people I ever get a chance to meet, and it&#8217;s an opportunity to meet my &#8220;tribe&#8221;. People who do the same type of work I do, for the same types of reasons.  And people who have so much to teach. Mostly I just thought I&#8217;d take the opportunity to talk to some folks and see if it would help me clear my mind about what the future may bring in terms of professional projects. In many ways it did. It helped me clear my mind on some issues, wipe some silly ideas from the rusty membrane, and fuel up on some much less silly ones instead. </p>
<p>I&#8217;m basically refuelled, ready to think long and hard about my continuing role in the non-profit sector. I&#8217;ve always felt that if I didn&#8217;t have the passion and the skills to make a difference, then I might as well step back into the for-profit sector once again. I&#8217;ve had 3 days of intense discussions on topics as diverse as mobile security, founders syndrome and non-profit mgmt, writing books as documentation and ensuring that your non-profit remains value-driven rather than feature-driven. Luckily those 3 days of drinking from the firehose has left me convinced that I still have the skills and the passion to make a difference. </p>
<p>Now for the hard part: figuring out how to lay that puzzle in such a way that I can also contribute a little bit to the family upkeep. Wish me luck.  </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2011/11/20/non-profit-software-developers-summit/">Non-profit software developers summit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">804</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This week I resigned my job at Refugees United</title>
		<link>/index.php/2011/10/14/this-week-i-resigned-my-job-at-refugees-united/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 11:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Me]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Refunite]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=678</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After just over 2 years and some great successes, matched by some great frustrations, I finally decided to quit my job as CTO of Refugees United. I&#8217;m currently on paternity leave, until January 1st, which neatly coincides with the end of my contract there. As to the reasons for leaving, well, we can chalk it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2011/10/14/this-week-i-resigned-my-job-at-refugees-united/">This week I resigned my job at Refugees United</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After just over 2 years and some great successes, matched by some great frustrations, I finally decided to quit my job as CTO of Refugees United. I&#8217;m currently on paternity leave, until January 1st, which neatly coincides with the end of my contract there. As to the reasons for leaving, well, we can chalk it down to frustrations over a lack of defined strategy, and some deep-felt disagreement about how to get the maximum impact from the available funding. I&#8217;m a passionate guy, and when it comes to passion and beliefs, probably not as compromising as I could be, and the founders have a very clear vision for what they want. Those 2 things collided. </p>
<p>I&#8217;m not going to go into a lot more detail in a public forum, for what should be obvious reasons, but I will say that it&#8217;s been a frustrating summer, and that I&#8217;m not the only one who&#8217;s left Refugees United in the past few months.</p>
<p>Refugees United is currently recruiting a new CEO, and I wish whomever that may be, the best of luck in the future. And I do, sincerely, hope that the vision (of providing a tool that empowers refugees to get involved in their own search for family) ultimately succeeds.</p>
<p>As for what the future holds, a person I trust recently invited me to have a &#8220;speculative wander through future opportunities&#8221;, and I like that phrase so much that I think that&#8217;s just what I&#8217;ll spend the next few months on. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2011/10/14/this-week-i-resigned-my-job-at-refugees-united/">This week I resigned my job at Refugees United</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">678</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>open source :: The Unbound Book</title>
		<link>/index.php/2011/09/06/open-source-the-unbound-book/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2011 06:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Free Software]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Me]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[non-profit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=670</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In April 2011 I gave a presentation on BookSprints and Booki at the excellent Unbound Book Conference in Amsterdam. Today a only partially related google search uncovered this blog post. Apart from frequent and varied misspellings of my name, it&#8217;s a decent summary of the discussion I brought to the table. Wireless and F/OSS geek [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2011/09/06/open-source-the-unbound-book/">open source :: The Unbound Book</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In April 2011 I gave a presentation on BookSprints and <a href="http://booki.cc/">Booki</a> at the excellent Unbound Book Conference in Amsterdam. Today a only partially related google search uncovered this blog post. Apart from frequent and varied misspellings of my name, it&#8217;s a decent summary of the discussion I brought to the table.</p>
<blockquote><p>Wireless and F/OSS geek and grassroots technology generalist Thomas Krag introduced Booksprint to the Open Source Publishing Tools workshop as an inverse story about the matter-ing of publishing: “..an outsider’s view of this whole book thing.”</p>
<p>via <a href="http://networkcultures.org/wpmu/unboundbook/tag/open-source/">open source :: The Unbound Book</a>.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2011/09/06/open-source-the-unbound-book/">open source :: The Unbound Book</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">670</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>As of february 1st I&#8217;m an employee of the Danish state.</title>
		<link>/index.php/2009/01/18/as-of-february-1st-im-an-employee-of-the-danish-state/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/2009/01/18/as-of-february-1st-im-an-employee-of-the-danish-state/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 13:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Me]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=551</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Strange but quite exciting. I accepted a job offer from the danish state, more specifically Statens IT, where i&#8217;ll be part of a ridiculously ambitious project to consolidate IT systems from more than a hundred government offices over the next 3-4 years. I never pictured myself as a government employee, it&#8217;s quite a strange transition [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2009/01/18/as-of-february-1st-im-an-employee-of-the-danish-state/">As of february 1st I&#8217;m an employee of the Danish state.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Strange but quite exciting. I accepted a job offer from the danish state, more specifically <a href="http://statens-it.dk/">Statens IT</a>, where i&#8217;ll be part of a ridiculously ambitious project to consolidate IT systems from more than a hundred government offices over the next 3-4 years. </p>
<p>I never pictured myself as a government employee, it&#8217;s quite a strange transition from freelancing, developing world do-gooder, but:</p>
<p>* It&#8217;s new and very much different.<br />
* It&#8217;s family friendly, and will allow me to pick Arthur up from day-care most days.<br />
* It&#8217;ll be chaotic, unpredictable and probably very interesting.<br />
* I can get unpaid leave for a few weeks a year in case there are <a href="http://booksprint.info/">book sprints</a>, workshops or otherwise i just can&#8217;t live without.<br />
* It comes with a stable, albeit modest, income, which will help us get rid of our mortgage, and perhaps do something crazy sometime in the future.<br />
* The whole project is unpredictable enough that nobody knows what will happen there after the first few years, which means i can keep a mental image in my mind of this as a temporary 2-4 year thing.</p>
<p>In general, i&#8217;m happy with the decision, the job and the general outlook of my near future.</p>
<p>I am however sad that there&#8217;s been so little time and energy for the developing world projects i really love. But it fels like an inevitable consequence of fatherhood.  </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2009/01/18/as-of-february-1st-im-an-employee-of-the-danish-state/">As of february 1st I&#8217;m an employee of the Danish state.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/2009/01/18/as-of-february-1st-im-an-employee-of-the-danish-state/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">551</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shameless self-promotion</title>
		<link>/index.php/2008/09/16/shameless-self-promotion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 09:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ict4dev]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Me]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[non-profit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wireless]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/2008/09/shameless-self-promotion/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite having kept a low profile, and done next to no development-related work in the past 2 years, a old journalist contact of wire.less.dk gave me a call yesterday, and today there&#8217;s a&#160; couple of decent quotes on danish on-line computer mag version2. It&#8217;s an article (in danish) about Tim Berners-Lee&#8217;s World Wide Web Foundation, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2008/09/16/shameless-self-promotion/">Shameless self-promotion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite having kept a low profile, and done next to no development-related work in the past 2 years, a old journalist contact of <a href="http://wire.less.dk/">wire.less.dk</a> gave me a call yesterday, and today there&#8217;s <a href="http://www.version2.dk/artikel/8465?nyhedsbrev">a&nbsp; couple of decent quotes</a> on danish on-line computer mag <a href="http://www.version2.dk/">version2</a>. </p>
<p>It&#8217;s an article (in danish) about <a href="http://www.webfoundation.org/donations/knight2008/tbl-speech">Tim Berners-Lee&#8217;s World Wide Web Foundation</a>, and his claims that we need to focus on extending the web to those 4 billion people who still aren&#8217;t properly on-line. His is a hard point to argue with, and i got away with spewing some very un-controversial answers to the usual questions, i.e. Do they really need the web? and what do they need it for? isn&#8217;t it hard when there&#8217;s no clean drinking water and no electricity?</p>
<p>I&#8217;m not going to bore anyone here with the obvious answers, but all-in-all the journalist did a decent job, only misspelling my name once in 4 mentions, and getting almost the entire name of our non-profit correct (it&#8217;s wire.less.dk rather than just wire.less).</p>
<p>perhaps this means i&#8217;m forgiven, not forgotten?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2008/09/16/shameless-self-promotion/">Shameless self-promotion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">523</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BookSprint: Thinking about the non-profit technology space</title>
		<link>/index.php/2008/05/22/booksprint-thinking-about-the-non-profit-technology-space/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 13:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[blogs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Free Software]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Me]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[non-profit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wireless]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/2008/05/booksprint-thinking-about-the-non-profit-technology-space/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>5 years of wireless wizardry, a very successful book project, some time out as a linux enterprise consultant, some time spent combining my technology skills with my interest in africa, and a good 6 months mostly hanging out with the future. I&#8217;m now spending a lot of time thinking about what the next 2 years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2008/05/22/booksprint-thinking-about-the-non-profit-technology-space/">BookSprint: Thinking about the non-profit technology space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>5 years of <a href="http://wire.less.dk/">wireless wizardry</a>, a very successful <a href="http://wndw.net/">book project</a>, some time out as a <a href="http://casalogic.dk/">linux enterprise consultant</a>, some time spent combining my technology skills with my <a href="http://allafrica.com/">interest in africa</a>, and a good 6 months mostly hanging out with <a href="http://flickr.com/photos/tkrag/sets/72157594550688898">the future</a>. I&#8217;m now spending a lot of time thinking about what the next 2 years could/should bring. </p>
<p>The technology non-profit space, web 2.0, free (open source) software, open networks, open content books, africa, and small kids. These are some of the things i&#8217;ve racked up some experience in over the last few years. There&#8217;s little doubt that the book project is the most impressive project i&#8217;ve had a hand in. With litterally hundreds of thousands of downloads (250,000 since february 2008), a 2nd edition, and official translations into spanish, french and arabic, this is one hell of a success for what is essentially a double niche-in-a-niche project. A technology book about wireless networks, targetted specifically at developing world practitioners. Yet the success if unequivocal, impressive, and ultimately has very little to do with my involvement.</p>
<p>I came up with a model that seems to work, found a little bit of funding to try it out, and invited the perfect team of authors. I also used my charm to convince <a href="http://hackerfriendly.com/">the best technical editor and author</a> i know to spend enormous amounts of time on very little money to help make this book as amazing as it is. Then i stepped back, went off and did some of the other stuff i mentioned above, and watched this idea unfold. </p>
<p>I&#8217;m proud of what i helped create, but also well aware of the role i played in it. But I want this success to be replicated, and there are a number of titles i think deserve to be written which could help create a series of pragmatic, hands-on technology books with a focus on the developing world, and free (open source) software. Published under some form of open content license, ensuring they reach their maximum potential as tools for communities around the world. </p>
<p>Not only do i think this is possible, but i also think it&#8217;s important in ways that i can&#8217;t yet quite describe in simple words, having to do with open content licenses, books as conveyors of learning, and the importance of technology independence. </p>
<p>Unlike other open content publishing business models, there&#8217;s a little twist in this one, since the prime source of income won&#8217;t be from book sales or advertising, but will come directly from funders, for whom the value-proposition should be pretty clear. Given the <a href="http://booksprint.info/">book sprint</a> model, we can produce pofessionally edited books at a fraction of the cost of the traditional publishing industry. And we have shown that these books are useful as training materials for workshops, as hands-on guides for individuals and organisations trying to implement these technologies, and as awareness raisers for decision-makers looking at technology solutions to exisiting problems. And the price point for a single title seems to be close to that of a single regional week-long technology workshop. So for the price of a single workshop, a book can be published that can become a tangible input to future workshops, but also can massively expand the reach of a workshop-based training model by reaching an audience far beyond that of the equivalent workshop. </p>
<p>And given some of the fascinating discussions i&#8217;ve seen on <a href="http://manypossibilities.net/2008/04/building-the-demand-in-print-on-demand/">pricing models</a> for <a href="http://radar.oreilly.com/archives/2008/02/community-pricing-for-books.html">open content books</a>, those costs would be shareable between multiple funders, by collecting bids before initiating the project. A model that could perhaps be combined with a <a href="http://magnatune.com/">magnatune</a>, <a href="http://magnatune.com/info/model">pay-what-you-feel-is-right</a> model for downloads. The profits of which could be shared with the authors, and help fund the day-to-day running of the organisation. If the costs of publishing the book has already been covered by non-profit funders, the post-production sales might help fund the difficult overhead that always dogs non-profits between projects. </p>
<p>Somewhere in this model there may even be room for experimenting with <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Social_business">Social Business</a> models, in the spirit of <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad_Yunus">Mohammad Yunus</a>. But that&#8217;ll be a discussion for another day, and perhaps another blog. </p>
<p></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2008/05/22/booksprint-thinking-about-the-non-profit-technology-space/">BookSprint: Thinking about the non-profit technology space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">510</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Looking for my next gig&#8230;.</title>
		<link>/index.php/2008/04/30/looking-for-my-next-gig/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/2008/04/30/looking-for-my-next-gig/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 20:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[blogs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Me]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/2008/04/looking-for-my-next-gig/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Questions:Startup or Job? Poor and excited or well-payed and constrained? Keywords: Free Software / Linux / Green IT / Mgmt / Evangelism / Developing world / Training Idea 1: Linux Training Company for Enterprise Linux training (Danish Market). Using freelancers to provide kick-ass linux enterprise training to the danish market. Probably with some attempt at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2008/04/30/looking-for-my-next-gig/">Looking for my next gig&#8230;.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Questions:<br />Startup or Job? Poor and excited or well-payed and constrained?</p>
<p>Keywords: Free Software / Linux / Green IT / Mgmt / Evangelism / Developing world / Training</p>
<p>Idea 1: Linux Training Company for Enterprise Linux training (Danish Market). Using freelancers to provide kick-ass linux enterprise training to the danish market. Probably with some attempt at adding African training activities to the mix. </p>
<p>Option 2: Project Mgmt job in the web industry. Good, stable pay. Opportunities for saving up some money for later investment into a startup or non-profit. </p>
<p>Problem: I&#8217;m not sure how to make all my personal goals meet. Having time for my wonderful family, making a difference, having fun at work, with strong challenges and good colleagues, and paying the bills. How?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2008/04/30/looking-for-my-next-gig/">Looking for my next gig&#8230;.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/2008/04/30/looking-for-my-next-gig/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">509</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>More photos of Arthur</title>
		<link>/index.php/2007/03/20/more-photos-of-arthur/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2007 12:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Me]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.multiplicity.dk/?p=502</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>My beautiful son is now 1 month old, and for his birthday yesterday, he got his own on-line photo-album at google, as well as his own e-mail address and domain name. More photos here</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2007/03/20/more-photos-of-arthur/">More photos of Arthur</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>My beautiful son is now 1 month old, and for his birthday yesterday, he got his own on-line photo-album at google, as well as his own e-mail address and domain name. </p>
<p><a href="http://picasaweb.google.com/arthur.ak/">More photos here</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/index.php/2007/03/20/more-photos-of-arthur/">More photos of Arthur</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">krag.be</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">502</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
